Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1912-1936
  - Subseries 1: General Manuscripts
    - Merrick, A.T. Merrill, K.P. Merrill, T.W. Merrill, Merryman, Meschter, Messenger, Messer (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Mesterton Methany, Metz, Metzler, A.N.Meyer, E.V. Meyer, G.P. Meyer (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Michael of Saxony, M. Michelson, P.O. Michelson, Michigan Authors Association, Mickels, Middlebury College, L. Middleton, S. Middleton (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - The Midland, Migel, Milam, J. Miles, M.M. Miles, S. Miles, K. Millay (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - A.W.R. Miller, B. Miller, E.H. Miller, E.V.D. Miller, F.R. Miller, Harold Miller, Harry Miller (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - H.A. Miller, J.C. Miller, J.F. Miller, J.S. Miller (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - M. Miller, N. Miller, R.F. Miller, T. Miller, W.G. Miller (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Milles, Millet, A.W. Mills, C. Mills, C.E. Mills, E.S. Mills (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - C.A. Millspaugh (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Milner, Minshall, Minster, Mirick, Mischkind, Mitalsky, B. Mitchell, E.S. Mitchell (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - G.S. Mitchell, J. Mitchell, R.C. Mitchell, S.V. Mitchell, W. Mitchell, Mitre Press, Mixter (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Modean, Moe, Moeller, Moffett, Mondini, Mondragon, Mongay, Monk (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - J.H. Monroe, L.D. Monroe, W.S. Monroe, Montenegro, E.S. Montgomery, L. Montgomery (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - R.M. Montgomery, Monypenny, Moodey, H. Moody, J. Moody Schmalz, A. Moore (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - C. Moore, E.H. Moore, E.M. Moore, F.D. Moore, G. Moore, M.K. Moore, N. Moore, S.P. Moore (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - T. Sturge Moore (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - V. Moore (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Ethel Moorhead (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - A. More, B. More, Angela Morgan, Anna Morgan, E. Morgan, M. Morgan, O. Morley (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - C. Morley, Morrell, Morrill (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Harrison S. Morris (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - I.M. Morris, J.G. Morris, L.R. Morris, L.S. Morris, R.L. Morris, T.B. Morris, F. Morrison, T. Morrison, W.A. Morrison, Morrissette (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Morrisson, Morrow, E.W. Morse, I. Morse, K.D. Morse, S.F. Morse, A. Morton, D. Morton, Marion Moses, Montrose Moses (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - W.R. Moses (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Mosig, Moss, Mossman, Mostov, Motvani (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Thomas Moult (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mounts, Mountsier, Mourer, Mower, Mowery, Mukerji, Mulfinger, Mulhall, Mulheron (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - J. Muller, O. Muller, Mullins, Mullowney, Munson, Münsterberg, C.R. Murphy (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - D. Murphy, G.M. Murray, I. Murray, Murrell, C.H. Musgrave, P. Musgrave, Musser, Myers (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Naff, Naidu, A.G. Nash, R. Nash, Nathan, Navarre, Navarro, Nawn (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Naylon, Needham, J.S. Neff, P. Neff, A. Nelson, C.B. Nelson, E.W. Nelson, Nestor (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Nethercot, Neugass, E. Neville, H. Neville, Newberry, Newbolt, Newhall, Newis (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - C.H. Newman, I. Newman, S. Newman, A. Newton, C. Newton, K. Newton, M.K. Newton, Ney (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Louise Townsend Nicholl, Lee Nichols, Leonora Nichols (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Robert Nichols (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - E. Nicolson, J. Nicolson, Niedecker, Nienaber, Noakes (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Yone Noguchi (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Nolte, Norcross, Norden, C. Norman, D. Norman, H.G. Norman, Norris (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - D. North, K. North, S. North, Northcliffe, Northe, Northrop, G. Northrop, Northwestern University (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - E. Norton, J. Norton, Nosser, Notre Dame Academy, Nott, Nourse, Novak, Noyes, Nussbaum (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Howard Nutt, L. Nutt, Nutter (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Oaks, Oates, Oberholtzer, O'Bolger, E.J. O'Brien (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - H.V. O'Brien, J. O'Brien, S.O'Brien, O'Byrne, O'Connor, A. O'Conor, N.J. O'Conor (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Charles L. O'Donnell (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - George Marion O'Donnell (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - P. O'Donnell, O'Farachain, O.gbiirn, Ogden, O'Gorman, O'Halloran, O'Horan, Oleson (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Olin, J. Oliver, Mn. Oliver, M.J.G. Oliver, W. Oliver, Olivers, R. Olmsted, S. Olmsted, L. Olson (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Charles Oluf Olsen (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - L. Olson, T. Olson, Olwell (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - O'Malley, O'Mara, B. O'Neil, D. O'Neil (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - G. O'Neil, O'Neill, Opdyche, Oppen (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - J. Oppenheim, J.J. Oppenheim, Orean, Ormond, Orr, Orton, Osawa, Osborne (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Osgood, O'Sheel, Ostenso, Osterman, Ostojic, O'Sullivan, Oswald (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Otis, The Outrider, L. Owen, O. Owen, E. Owens, E.P. Owens (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Pach, Pachman, Paddock, Padovano, Paebar, C.H. Page (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - F.S. Page, Paget, Pailthorpe, E. Palmer, F. Palmer, H.E. Palmer, H.R. Palmer, J.R. Palmer (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - P. Palmer, Panelle, Paquette, Paradise, Parke, L.F. Parker (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - P. Parker, V.M. Parker, W.H. Parker, W.R. Parker, Parks, Parmenter, G. Parsons, M.R. Parsons (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Partridge, Patee, Joan Paterson, John Paterson, R.H. Paterson, Pathfinder, Sister Patrice, D.D. Patrick (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - H. Patrick, R. Patrick, Patten, A. Patterson, W.M. Patterson, Paulig (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Paulmier, Pava, Pavich, Payer, A.B. Payne, L.W. Payne, Payson (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - H. Pearce, T.W. Pearce, L.H. Pearson, Pease (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - D.C. Peattie, E.W. Peattie, L.R. Peattie, E.H. Pennell, J.S. Pennell (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Percival, Percy, Perdue, Perez, Pergament, Perkins (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Perkoff, Perlzweig, C. Perry, C.H. Perry, L.C. Perry, Peterkin (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Julie M. Peterkin (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Peterson, Petgen, Petrunkevitch, Pettengill, Pettus, Peyton (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Pfund, Phelpot, A.L. Phelps, C. Phelps, E. Phelps, W.L. Phelps (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Phillips, B. Phillips, C. Phillips, M. Phillips, P.H. Phillips, R.M. Phillips (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - S. Phillips, W. Phillips, W.K. Phillips, B.P. Phipps, E. Phipps, Phlegar, Picola, Pieczonka (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - B. Pierce, C.A. Pierce, G.C. Pierce, R.E. Pierce, Piercy, B.B. Pierson, R.B. Pierson, Pietsch (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Piffard, Pihlman, Pike, Pilant, Piller, Pillin, Pillionnel (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Pinckney, Pinder, Pinglay (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Edwin Ford Piper (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Piper, Piser, Pittala, Pitts, P. Pitts (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Platt, Plotkin, Plotnik, G. Plunkett, J. Plunkett, Poda, Poetry Clan, Poetry Forum, Poetry Review/Poetry Society, Poetry Society of America, Poetry Week (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Pollett, Pollitt, Pollock, Poovey, C. Porter, K.W. Porter, P. Porter (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Posegate, Post, M.B. Post, Postgate (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Potamkin, Potocki, Potter, Potts, Poulsen, H.L. Pound (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - L. Pound, A.M. Powell, S.W. Powell, Power, E. Powers, J. Powers, J.C. Powys, L. Powys (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - E.J. Pratt, F. Pratt, Preller, Pressley, A. Preston (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Ethel Preston, Etta Preston, E.E. Preston, J.H. Preston, K. Preston, Pretzman (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Preuss, A.M. Price, J.M. Price, R.C. Price, R.E. Price, R.G. Price, A. Priest, G.W. Priest (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Priestman, Prince, Princell, Prindiville, Prindle, Prix Femina Americain (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Probst, Probstfield (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Frederic Prokosch (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - A.H. Proudfoot, H. Proudfoot, Prouty, Provines, Pryor, Pudney (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Pullen, Pulse, H. Pulsifer, S. Pulsifer, Purcell (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Idella Purnell (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Purvis, E. Putnam, S. Putnam, Putt (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Quarles, Quesney, J. Quinn, J.R. Quinn (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Kerker Quinn (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Rabinowitch, A. Radcliffe, Radford, Raines (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Carl Rakosi (Callman Rawley) (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Raley, Rall, Ramie, Ramsay, F. Ramsey, H. Ramsey, E. Rand, S. Rand, Randall-Mills, Raney (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Ransom, Rao, Raphael, Rapson, Rascoe, Raskin (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Dorothy Una Ratcliffe (Box 19, Folder 28-30)
    - Rathbone, Ravenel, Raworth, Ray, Rayford, J.L. Rayford, B. Raymund, R. Raymund (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Rea, Read, Reade, Reavey (Read SEE ALSO OVERSIZE) (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Rebel Poets, Reckill, Record, Redfield, B. Reed, D. Reed, E. Reed, I. Reed (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - John S. Reed (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - L. Reed, Reeder, Rees (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Lizette Woodworth Reese, Reeth (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Paul Eaton Reeve (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Reeves, Regester, Regill, Reibling (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Dorothy E. Reid (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - H. Reid, P. Reid, Reifsteck, Reinhardt, Reinstein, Reisman, Remington, Remisoff, Renaud, Reno (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Replansky, Repplier, Reque, Retchell, Rethey (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Kenneth Rexroth (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Reznard, Charles Reznikoff (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Rhibault, The Rhymers' Club, Ernest Rhys (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - H.M. Rice, J.P. Rice, L.L. Rice, M. Rice, R. Rice, W. Rice (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Rich, H.T. Rich, P. Rich, B. Richards (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - E.A. Richards, E.E. Richards, G.M. Richards, L. Richards, M.H. Richards, C.C. Richardson, D.L. Richardson (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Dorothy M. Richardson (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - M.K. Richardson, Richter, Ridder (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Lola Ridge (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
    - Ridley, Rieber, Rigg, K. Riggs, Lynn Riggs (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Riker, H. Riley, L. Riley, Rinehart, Riordan, Ritchell, Ward Ritchie, Wyn Ritchie (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Jessie B. Rittenhouse (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Margaret Todd Ritter (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Rivers, F. Rivola, G. Rivola (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - E. Robbins, R.C. Robbins, A.H. Roberts, B.P. Roberts, C. Roberts, C.G.D. Roberts, C.W. Roberts, H.B. Roberts (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Michael Roberts (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - P. Roberts, E.A. Robertson, L.D. Robertson, Robilant, A. Robinson, C.R. Robinson (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Donald Fay Robinson (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Eloise Robinson (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - F. Robinson, G. Robinson, T.O. Robinson, Roche, Rockel, Rodell, Roden (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - S.E. Rodger, Roditi (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - John Rodker (Box 20, Folder 30-31)
    - Selden Rodman (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Robert Roe (Box 20, Folder 33-35)
    - T. Rogers, M.S. Rogers, T. Rogers, E. Rolfe, T. Rolfe, L. Rollins, R. Rollins, Rolt-Wheeler (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Romatka, Romig, Rooke, Rooney, E.M. Root, J.W. Root, T. Root, F.N. Roper, H.D. Roper (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - James Rorty (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Rosary College, Rosborough, B. Rose, E. Rose, F. Rose, I.R.C.Rose, W. Rose, A. Rosen (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - M. Rosen, Rosenbaum (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Harold Rosenberg (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
    - Isaac Rosenberg, Rosenburg (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Harry Roskolenkier (later, Roskolenko) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - C. Ross, M.W. Ross (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - P.W. Ross, V.B. Ross, W.W.E. Ross (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Samuel Roth (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Rothrock, Roughton, Roush,, Rowan (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Rubin, Ruble, Ruby, Rummons, Rumry (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Runbeck, Runner, Rush, Rushton, E. Russ, P. Russ (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - A.D. Russell, A.J. Russell, B. Russell, C.E. Russell (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - M. Russell, S.K. Russell, U.K. Russell, Russmann (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Grace Dorcas Ruthenburg (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ruthven, Rutland, Rutledge, Ruttle, C. Ryan (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - James J. Ryan (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
    - K.W. Ryan, Ryerson, Ryskind, Rysley (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Sabalala, Sabel, Sabin (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Sadler, Safford, Safier, C.B. Sage, J. Sage, Sagmaster, Sahl, Saint Gauden (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - St. Hilaire, St. Jean, St. John Swezey, Sakaniki, Salemson, Salinger, Salisbury (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - B. Salkeld, C. Salkeld, Salkin, A. Salmon, D. Salmon (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Sydney S. Salt (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Salter, Salvatore, Samkey, A. Sampson, H. Sampson, Sampter, Samsel, Sanborn (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Robert A. Sanborn (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - A. Sanders, C. Sanders, E.V. Sanders, G.W. Sanders (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ottys Sanders (Box 21, Folder 30-31)
    - Sanderson, Sandquist, Sands, Sandwell (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Sangster, Saper, Saphier (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Edward Sapir (Box 21, Folder 34-35)
    - Sarbach (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Lew Sarett (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
    - L. Sargent, P. Sargent, S. Sargent (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - May Sarton (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Siegfried Sassoon, The Saturday Review, Saul, H. Saunders, M. Saunders, W. Saunders (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Derek S. Savage (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - M.J. Savage, Saw, A. Sawyer, W. Sawyer, M.R. Sawyers, Saxon (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Scallin, Scallon, Schacht, Schappes, G.C. Schauffler, R.C. Schauffler (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - R.H. Schauffler, E.T. Scheffauer, H. Scheffauer, Scheffer (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Schermerhorn, R. Schermerhorn, F. Schevill (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - M.E. Schevill, Schiddel, Schlichter, Schloss, Schmidt, Schmitt (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Isidor Schneider (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - The Scholastic, Schoonmaker, Schramm, Schriftgiesser, Schubert, Schultz (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Schutze, Schware, D. Schwartz, M. Schwartz, W.L. Schwartz (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Scollard, A.B. Scott, C.A.D. Scott, E. Scott (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Evelyn Bartlett Scott (Box 22, Folder 19-20)
    - F.N. Scott, J.P. Scott, M. Scott, V. Scott (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Winfield Townley Scott (Box 22, Folder 22-23)
    - Scripps, Anderson M. Scruggs (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - J.E. Scruggs (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Scullion, Scupham, Seager, Searing (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sears, Searson, Sebbelov, Sebree-Smith, Seeley, Seibel, Seibert, A. Seiffert, H.S. Seiffert (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Marjorie Allen Seiffert (Box 22, Folder 28-31)
    - Seldes, Sell, de la Selva (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Selway, Semper, D.K. Sen, S.D. Sen, R. Sergel, R.P. Sergel (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Sewell, Sewland, Sexton, F.W. Seymour, G.S. Seymour, M.F. Seymour, R. Seymour (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Shafer, Shah, Shakespeare, Shanafelt (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Shanahan, J. Shapiro, R. Shapiro, Sharman, Shaull, C. Shaw (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - D.S. Shaw, E. Shaw, F. Shaw, N. Shaw Shearer (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Sheffield, E. Sheldon, M.W. Sheldon, Shelley, I. Shepard, O. Shepard, E.M. Shepherd, H.B. Shepherd (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Shera, Sherbon, Sherburn, Sherby, J.D. Sheridan, M.A. Sheridan, B.W. Sherman, F.D. Sherman, S.P. Sherman, Sherrell (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Laura Sherry (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
    - P.A. Sherry, R.F. Sherry, C.L. Sherwood, G.B. Sherwood, Shields, Shinigu, Shipley, Shippey, Shisler, Shoemaker, Shores (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Shorey, C. Shorter, E. Shorter, Shortridge, Shreiber, Shuey, Shuford, Shugio (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Shui, Shuler, Shull, Shumaker, Shuman, Shumway, Shyn (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Siat, Sickels, Sidlers, Sieg, Sifton, Sigmund (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Siler, Sill, Silvay, Silvere, Silverman, Bayard Simmons (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - B. Simmons, C.D. Simmons, J.R. Simmons, L. Simmons, H.A. Simons (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - M. Simpson, S. Simpson (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - W.H. Simpson, J. Sinclair (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - M. Sinclair, S. Sinclair, Sinclaire, Singh, A. Singleton, S. Singleton, Sisk-Noyes, Skavlan, Skeel, Skeen (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Constance Skinner (Box 23, Folder 16-19)
    - F. Skinner, J.C. Skinner, J.L. Skinner, W.E. Skinner, Slader, Slappey, Slater, B. Sleeper, H.D. Sleeper, J. Sloan, J.V. Sloan, M.B. Sloan (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Slobod, Slocum, Sloss, Slye (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Florence S. Small (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - A. Smith, A.G. Smith (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - A.J.M. Smith (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - B. Smith, Clark Ashton Smith (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Caroline Parker Smith, Chard Powers Smith (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Carrie W. Smith, Clara W. Smith (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - D.L. Smith, E.O. Smith, E.S. Smith, F. Smith, G.A. Smith, H.J. Smith (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - H.P. Smith, H.W. Smith, I. Smith, J.E. Smith (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - L. Smith, L.A.K. Smith, L.W. Smith, M.C. Smith, M.P. Smith, R. Smith, W.B. Smith, The Smith Alumnae Quarterly (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Smyth, Smythe (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Smytheman, Snelgrove, Snell, Snelling, Sniffen, R. Snow, R.K. Snow (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Wilbert Snow (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - R.K. Snow, G.W. Snyder, W.H. Snyder, Solle, Soule, Soultar, Sousa, Soutar, Southerland (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Southern, Spain (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Sparks, Spates, Speare, Speer, Speight, E. Spencer (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Lilian White Spencer (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
    - M.L. Spencer (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Leonora Speyer (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
    - Spicer, Spier, Spoerl, Sprague, Spratt, Sprietsing, Squire (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Stabler, Stafford, Stahl, Stahlberg, Stalher, Stalling, Stallman,, Standew (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Standlee, Stanford, E.S. Stanley, L. Stanley, M.E. Stanley, Stanley-Wrench, C.S. Stanton, T. Stanton (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Stapleton, E.D. Starbuck, V. Starbuck, H. Starrett, M. Starrett, V. Starrett (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Stead, Stearn, F. Stearns, H.C. Stearns, M.M. Stearns, Stecker (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Steele, Steig, Steiger (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - L. Stein, Steinmetz, Stepanchev (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - J. Stephens, M.H. Stephens, M.J. Stephens, W. Stephens (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - George Sterling (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Sterner, Sterrett, B. Stevens, F. Stevens, H. Stevens, M.W. Stevens, T.W. Stevens (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - B.E. Stevenson, E.B. Stevenson, K.N. Stevenson, Steward, A.M. Stewart, H.W. Stewart (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - I. Stewart, L. Stewart, O.G. Stewart, R. Stewart, Stewart-Tattersall (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Stifler, Still, A.B. Stillman, E.C. Stillman, M.W. Stillman (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Stockett, P. Stoddard, H. Stoddard, Stolz, L. Stone, M. Stone, P. Stone (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - W.J. Stone, Stopher, Storer (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Storey, Stork (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - M. Storm, P. Storm (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - P. Strand, Stratton-Porter, Straub, Straubel, Streamer, Street (Street SEE Heard) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Arthur Stringer (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Marion Strobel (Box 24, Folder 27-28)
    - Strode, K. Strong, L.A.G. Strong (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Stroup, C.D. Stuart, F. Stuart, H. Stuart (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Jessie Stuart (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - M. Stuart, R. Stuart, Stuby, Stutz, Styles (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Subido, Suckow, Sueur, A. Sullivan, A.M. Sullivan (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - D.C. Sullivan, M. Sullivan, Summers, Sumner, Sun (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Sunny, Sutherland, Sutton, Swain, E. Swan, J. Swan, Swanson, Sward (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Swartz, J. Sweeney, J.J. Sweeney, Sweetkind, Swerig, Swezey, Swift (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Swing, Swingler, Sykes, E. Symanski, R. Symanski (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Symons (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - J. Symons, Syrian (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - R.G. Taber, S. Taber, Tai Jen, Taketomo, Talamon (S. Taber SEE ALSO OVERSIZE) (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Carlton Talbott (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - G. Talbott, E.B. Tallman, L. Tallman, R. Tallman, Tallquist (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Tamerlin, Tanasso, Tarr, C. Tate, Tatham, Tatum, Taupin (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - D. Taylor, F.B. Taylor, G.M. Taylor, G.W. Taylor, H.P. Taylor, M.M. Taylor, E. Teall, G. Teall (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Tefft, Telfair, Teller, Temple (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Ten Hoor, Poh Leng Teo, Terrell, Tesar (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - A.S.J. Tessimond (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Paul C. Tewkesbury (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Tewson, Thanhouser, B. Thayer, E.K. Thayer, E.P. Thayer, E.R. Thayer (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - H.M. Thayer, S.H. Thayer, Thayerman [or pseudonym, North Falcon] (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Theobald, Theophilus, C. Thomas, D.M. Thomas, Edward Thomas (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - G. Thomas, H. Thomas, K.G. Thomas, L.C. Thomas, L.E. Thomas, M.B. Thomas, R. Thomas (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Sister Thomas Aquinas (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - B. Thompson, D.K. Thompson, E.G. Thompson, F. Thompson, H.W. Thompson, I.B. Thompson (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - P. Thompson, R.B. Thompson, Slason Thompson, Stuart Thompson, W.B. Thompson, Thorburn (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - J.C. Thornton, W. Thornton, Thorp, Thudichum, Thurston, Tiebout, Tieken (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Ethel Arnold Tilden (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - F.A. Tilden, Tinker, Tinsley, Titus (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Todd, Todrin, E.C. Tomkins, J. Tomkins, Tomson, Toner, Tonkin (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Tonner, Toomer, Torgownik (Targ) (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Ridgely Torrence, Towley (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Charles Hanson Towne (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - N. Towne, B.A. Townsend, J.W. Townsend, Townshend (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - E.C. Tracy, P.E. Tracy (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Tramonti, Trapp (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - S. Trask, W. Trask (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Travsil, Travis, Trayner, Treadwell, Iris Tree, Trehame, Tremlete, Herbert Trench (Herbert Trench SEE ALSO OVERSIZE) (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Trepte, Trombly (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Troubetzkoy, Truck, Truesdale, I.S. Tucker, J.E. Tucker, K.M. Tucker, Tufts (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - C. Tull, J. Tull, Tung, Tupper (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Mark Turbyfill (Box 25, Folder 36-37)
    - Turnbull (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - A.N. Turner (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - E. Turner, J. Turner, K.M. Turner, L.C. Turner, N.B. Turner, M. Turpin (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Twinge, Twitchell, Twynham, C. Tyler, M. Tyler (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Parker Tyler (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Tynan Hinckson, Tyne, Tyson (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - G. Udell, Ullman, Ulrich, E.W. Underwood (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - J.C. Underwood, Unger (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Allan Updegraff (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Allan Upward (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
    - Uschold, Utley (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Vail, Vakil, Valentine, Valyear, Van Buskirk, Van Cleve, Vanderlip (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Vanderpyl, Van der Veer, Van Deusen, Van Dore, I. Van Doren, Mark Van Doren (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Vane, Van Lanahan, Van Male, Vann, Van Norman, Van Raalte (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Van Rein, Van Rensselaer, Van Slyke, Van Valkenburgh Vilas, Carl Van Vechten (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Van Volkenburg, Van Zindram, Varley, Varney, G. Vaughan, M. Vaughan (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Veider, Venable, Verdieres, Verrill, Verry, Verse, Vesely, Veysey, Vijaya-Tunga (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Charles Vildrac (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Vilipsons, Jose Garcia Villa (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - W.D. Vincent, Vines, Vinton (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Vliet, Von Strode, Vornholt, Vranopoulous (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Wade, C. Wagner (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Wagstaff, Waidelich, M. Waldron, W. Waldron (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Arthur Waley (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - E. Walker, H. Walker, J.P. Walker, M. Walker, N. Walker, R. Walker (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - S. Walker, Wallace, Wallach, Walleen, Waller, Walling, Wallis, Wallop (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Thomas Walsh, W. Walsh, Walters (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Eda Lou Walton (Box 26, Folder 29-30)
    - Wang, Wanger, Waples, K. Ward, L.L. Ward (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - May Williams Ward (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Olive Ward (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - W. Ward, Warlow, D. Warren, G.O. Warren, M.R. Warren (Box 26, Folder 34)